https://www.asapchecks.com/privacy-policy

Would you take a minute to let us know what you think of our new website?
Shop Early - Ship Early
All courier and mail carrier services are anticipating even higher than normal seasonal increased volumes of parcels and mail this year due to COVID-19. Normal delivery standards may not be possible during December and January.
Read our COVID-19 / Coronavirus Update
You are
signed in as:   |
My Account |
US SITE
Go to Canadian site
Bank quality checks without bank prices, ready to ship in 24 hours
Call: 888-852-4325
0
Click to see menu
Home
Compare & Save
Products & Pricing
Questions
Contact
ReOrder
ReOrder
Customer Login
Log Out
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or request an e-mail reminder for your next order.
Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number, credit card information or Billing Address and Shipping Address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Third party vendors, including Google and DoubleClick, use cookies and device identifiers to a) serve ads based on user's prior visits to our website b) provide anonymous interest and demographic data to help us better understand visitors to our websites. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.
Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
• To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
These security measures include: SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'My Account' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
CAN-SPAM Compliance
We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
This policy was last modified on May 26, 2014
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
ASAP Checks, Forms & Supplies, Inc.
13 Bethune Street #190
Alexandria Bay, NY 13607
USA
info@asapchecks.com
888-852-4325 (888-85-CHECK)
Privacy Policy Customer Pledge
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:
Federal Trade Commision Fair
California Online Privacy Protection Act
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act
Privacy Alliance
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form.
Respectfully,
Les C. Cseh President
www.asapchecks.com
Order Checks
BEGIN NEW ORDER
Reorder Checks
BEGIN REORDER BEGIN REORDER
I have been ordering from ASAP checks for years, and highly recommend them. Prices are very good, service is very quick and re-ordering on-line is a breeze.
– Tom
The checks were here in a timely manner and just what I ordered.
– Diane
The ASAP Checks promise
We pride ourselves on our superior product quality and attentive customer service. If for any reason you are unsatisfied with your order, simply return it for a hassle free refund.
All product names, brands and trademarks are property of their respective owners.
